[{"question": " happy birthday!!!", "answer": " happy birthday!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " rach! come on! rach!", "answer": " it\u0092s your birthday!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": "  she\u0092s not as pretty as she was when she was", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " they do!", "answer": " rachel! come on out! monica made breakfast!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " good ones?", "answer": " they all came from the list you handed out to us two weeks ago.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " well, can i keep the presents and still be 29?", "answer": " come on rach! look, turning thirty is not that big a deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " y\u0092know, i\u0092m still 29 in guam.", "answer": " hey, 30 is not that old! do you know how old the earth is?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " late thirties? oh come on you guys! is it just me? am i overreacting to this?", "answer": " no rach, it\u0092s not just you. my thirtieth birthday certainly wasn\u0092t that much fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " rach, you\u0092re in a great place in your life. come on, you\u0092ve got a great job! good friends\u009a", "answer": " yeah, you\u0092re roommate is a soap opera star.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " look, y\u0092know i know my life\u0092s going pretty well, but i look around and i just see so many people who\u0092ve accomplished so many other goals by the time they\u0092re thirty.", "answer": " yeah, but you shouldn\u0092t compare yourself to me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " come on phoebe! you can do it phoebe! come on!", "answer": " there you go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " thirty. ugh, i mean thirty! monica, do you remember mean, old mrs. kreeger in the fifth grade? she was thirty!", "answer": " come on, let\u0092s have some fun. huh?  what do you want to do today?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " nothing. i don\u0092t want to do anything.", "answer": " well, doing nothing on your thirtieth is better than doing something stupid, like ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " how hot do i look in this, huh?!", "answer": " ross, a sports car? wouldn\u0092t it have been cheaper to just stuff a sock down there?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " that\u0092s not what this is about okay? i-i am a sports car enthusiast. i have always been into cars.", "answer": " hey, what\u0092s the horsepower on this thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  i don\u0092t know, but-but look how shiny!", "answer": " i can\u0092t believe you bought this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " really! god ross, what were you thinking?  i know it\u0092s really shallow, but a part of me wants him again.", "answer": " oh, well get in line missy.  so, can i have a ride stud?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " y\u0092know what? i am going to do something today. i\u0092m not just gonna sit around like some old lady. i\u0092m gonna get something pierced. like my uh, like my nose or my tongue or something.", "answer": " really?! \u0091cause y\u0092know that hurts.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " so what?! y\u0092know what? the way i see it\u0097\u0097ow! son of a bitch!!", "answer": " look rachel, i know what you\u0092re going through. i\u0092m totally freaked about turning 25.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": "  get out, get out of my apartment.", "answer": " all right rach, for what it\u0092s worth, i think that you\u0092re doing great. i mean y\u0092know let\u0092s face it, no one handles this well.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " least of all you.", "answer": " why? what you\u0092d do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": "  would you put that back on?! monica\u0092s gonna be here any minute!", "answer": " but it hurt\u0092s my joey\u0092s apple.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  you\u0092ve done a wonderful job with this party chandler. everything looks so lovely.", "answer": " oh well, not as lovely as you. i mean, i can\u0092t believe that you would have a thirty-year-old daughter!  and you! i can\u0092t believe that you would have a tux that\u0092s thirty years old!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " it\u0092s older than that. ross was actually conceived right near this tuxedo.", "answer": " ohh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  hey! everybody hide! hide! i saw her! she\u0092s coming!", "answer": " okay! okay! everybody down! everybody down!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " hey-hey are you drunk?", "answer": " nooo!  okay.  whoa!  okay. see i was, i was a little nervous about turning  thirty.  so the bus boys took me out for some drinks.  i wanna puke on you later!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " okay, here is the thing. we have thrown a very formal surprise party for you in there! all of your friends are in there and your parents!", "answer": " noo!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " yes!", "answer": " noo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " yes!!", "answer": " oh no! my parents have never seen me drunk!  that they know of.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " okay, here\u0092s the thing. we\u0092re gonna get you some coffee and they will never know that you\u0092re drunk.", "answer": " really?! you promise?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " yeah, i\u0092ll take care of it.", "answer": " okay. i love you so much.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  okay we have to do something about your breath.", "answer": " what about your breath?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " that\u0092s still yours. okay, now remember it\u0092s a surprise party. so, when you go in, act surprised.", "answer": " okay. i can do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " okay, forward. forward\u0097stop!  okay, back\u0097stop!  okay, forward\u0097stop! stop! stop!", "answer": " ross, just forget about it. this guy\u0092s got you totally wedged", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": "  is this yours?", "answer": " well actually\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " dude, you soooo need this car.", "answer": "  okay. okay, here\u0092s what we\u0092re gonna do. okay, i\u0092m gonna break into this mini-van and put it in neutral. you guys push it forward so ross can drive out of his spot. okay? all right, here we go.  haul ass!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " happy thirtieth birthday! here!  it\u0092s for the child in you, and the woman. happy thirtieth!", "answer": " right, why do you keep saying that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " because it\u0092s our thirtieth birthday.", "answer": " yeah, no we\u0092re not thirty. we\u0092re 31. okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " oh, it\u0092s you.", "answer": " yeah. what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " yeah, we\u0092re not thirty, we\u0092re 31.", "answer": " nu-uh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " yea-huh! that\u0092s what is says on my birth certificate.", "answer": " you have your birth certificate?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah, i got a big box of family stuff when my mom died.", "answer": " our mom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " do you have my birth certificate?", "answer": " no, i sold it to a swedish runaway.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": "  oh my god! oh my god, we are 31.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " i just lost a whole year of my life.", "answer": "  okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " your middle name is pamela?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " well, i never knew mine. do you remember what it is?", "answer": " yes! phoebe.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " that\u0092s my first name.", "answer": " right, okay, then no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " okay before we start the celebration, monica has to go put on her party dress.", "answer": " yay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": "  paul!", "answer": "  phil.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " phil!", "answer": " now, there is a dress laid out on your bed.  okay,  you\u0092re doing great. you\u0092re doing great. you\u0092re doing fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " hey, what\u0092s going on?", "answer": " monica\u0092s a little drunk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " yay! i love drunk monica!", "answer": " awwwww\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  go change!  she doesn\u0092t want her parents to know she\u0092s drunk.", "answer": " ohh! all right! all right. here\u0092s what we\u0092ll do, i\u0092ll get twice as drunk as monica and then no one\u0092s will even notice her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " what\u0092s-what\u0092s going on? phil\u0092s really pissed!", "answer": " monica\u0092s wasted.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " maybe that will liven up this party.", "answer": "  okay, will you just go help her change please!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " okay, but taking care of a drunk, naked woman seems like a job for joey.", "answer": " yep.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": "  this one\u0092s from me.", "answer": " ahh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " it wasn\u0092t on your list, but hopefully you\u0092ll think it\u0092s really fun.", "answer": "  a scooter!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": "  stick to the list. always stick to the list.", "answer": " no! no-no, i love it. thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " okay, open ours next. open ours next!", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " now that you\u0092re a couple, we don\u0092t get two presents from you guys?", "answer": " for my last birthday you gave me a hug!  okay, read the card! read the card!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " okay.  happy birthday grandma! it\u0092s better to be over the hill  then buried under it.  all our love monica and chandler.  that\u0092s funny, yeah!", "answer": " no-no-no-no! that was the joke!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": "  no, i know! i get it! it\u0092s funny!", "answer": " no, because you\u0092re not a grandmother!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hey! look who\u0092s back! it\u0092s the birthday girl! how\u0092s the birthday girl feeling?", "answer": " well, i feel fine, but i think you\u0092re bumming out the rest of the kids.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " okay! y\u0092know what? i realized it was stupid to get upset about not having a husband and kids. all i really needed was a plan. see i wanna have three kids\u009a", "answer": " oh let me guess, and you wanna have them all at the same time and you wanna have them for your brother.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " as i was saying\u009a i should probably have the first of the three kids by the time i\u0092m 35 which gives me five years. i love this plan! i wanna marry this plan!", "answer": " if you could do that, i\u0092d marry the hippity-hop.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " so, if i wanna have my kid when i\u0092m 35, i don\u0092t have to get pregnant until i\u0092m 34. which gives prada four years to start making maternity clothes! oh wait, but i do want to be married for a year before i get pregnant\u009a", "answer": " really! that long?!   look all you want, it\u0092s happening!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " no, so i don\u0092t have to get married until i\u0092m 33! that\u0092s three years, that\u0092s three whole years\u0097oh, wait a minute though. i\u0092ll need a year and a half to plan the wedding, and i\u0092d like to know the guy for a year, year and a half before we get engaged\u009a which means i need to meet the guy by the time i\u0092m thirty.", "answer": " which is fine! because you just turned\u0097\u0097twenty-eight!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": "  i\u0092m telling you it\u0092s like watching bambi learn how to walk.", "answer": "  you\u0092re drunk! mom and dad are gonna be maaaaadd! maybe i\u0092m a little drunk.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": "  oh that\u0092s great! right there! can we get some of that over here please?  there we go.", "answer": "  hey! are those crab cakes?  did i not tell ya to come straight to me when more crab cakes were ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": "  how are you feeling?", "answer": " you are so handsome! i wanna make love to you right here, right now!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " i really wish that you wouldn\u0092t.", "answer": "  now all you have to do is just get through a little bit more, okay? then we can put you in bed, okay? just smile and don\u0092t talk to anyone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": "  speech! speech! let\u0092s hear from the birthday girl! huh?", "answer": " pheebs!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " don\u0092t you see? everyone\u0092s looking at me! the plan\u0092s working! i didn\u0092t even have to take off my top yet!", "answer": " speech! come on monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " come on!", "answer": " come on! speech!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": "  hey chandler, you can\u0092t keep your hands off her for one second!", "answer": " oh-ho, i think it\u0092s nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " i-i-i wanna thank you all for coming. my family and my friends\u009a", "answer": "  wooo!! hoo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " i lost a whole year! i can\u0092t believe it! this is so unfair!", "answer": " oh, i don\u0092t know pheebs. it\u0092ll be okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " will it? will it?! i mean, how would you feel if you found out you were 31?", "answer": " that\u0092s not gonna happen. no.  because we have a new deal!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " plus, it totally ruined my schedule! i\u009ai haven\u0092t done any of the things i wanted to do by the time i was 31!", "answer": " like what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " like okay i-i-i, i haven\u0092t met any portuguese people! i, i haven\u0092t had the perfect kiss! and i haven\u0092t been to sniper\u0092s school!", "answer": " phoebe, y\u0092know why don\u0092t we just go upstairs and have some birthday cake?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " hey.  oh, poor pheebs.", "answer": " hey, y\u0092know what you guys? i think i\u0092m gonna go walk her home.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " oh man!", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " pheebs! wait up!  listen uh, close your eyes.  maybe that\u0092s one thing you can cross off your list.", "answer": " oh yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " oh, and plus i\u0092m 1/16th portuguese.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " okay, is everybody clear? we\u0092re gonna pick it up\u009aand move it. now all we need is teamwork, okay? we\u0092re gonna lift the car\u009aand slide it out. lift and slide!", "answer": " ross, i really don\u0092t think\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  lift!! and slide!", "answer": " okay, here we go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " hey joey, can i\u009a", "answer": " oh, come on rach! my turn just started!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " actually, i just wanna talk to tag.", "answer": " oh. okay. hey, can i ride this outside?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " whatever! okay, i\u0092m not your mother.", "answer": " okay!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " not in the street!!", "answer": " yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": "  hi.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " how are you doing? are you feeling any better?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " yeah, i\u0092m doing okay. i\u0092m um\u009alet\u0092s talk.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " umm\u009a", "answer": " what\u0092s up?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " ohh tag, umm\u009ayou\u0092re such a great guy and we have sooo much fun together but i don\u0092t-i don\u0092t\u009a", "answer": " wait! i think i see where you\u0092re going, but before you say anything else, can i just say one more thing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " well said. and a uh good example of the fun i was referring to uhh, but i just think i\u0092m past the point where i think i can y\u0092know, just have fun.", "answer": " rachel, don\u0092t do this. this is just because you\u0092re turning thirty.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " yeah, it is! but you\u0092re just a kid! i mean you\u0092re 25!", "answer": " twenty-four actually.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " oh god! y\u0092know what i wish? i wish you were six years older. well actually, if i\u0092m wishin\u0092 for stuff, i actually wish i was six years younger.", "answer": " me too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " hey! how\u0092d it go?", "answer": " oh, if i only want two kids, can i keep him for another year?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " you did the right thing.", "answer": "  i don\u0092t like this anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " well, here we are, just a bunch of thirty year olds.", "answer": " god, do you realize in ten years we\u0092re gonna be 40?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " yes! my baby\u0092s finally free!", "answer": " all-all right!  start it up! let\u0092s go!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " you wanna buy a car?", "answer": " no.  ending credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s7/ep14.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}]